moviehotties.com 2017-11-22

# The JoBlo.com Privacy policy

**Privacy Statement for the JoBlo Movie Network**

The JoBlo Movie Network (JoBlo.com) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:

**Advertisers:  
**We currently use several outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies (see below). Cookies received with banner ads are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. Our site does not use cookies.

**Third Party Advertising  
**We use Gorilla Nation, IndieClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

**Third Party Cookies   
**In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique â€œcookieâ€ on your browser.

**Automatically Logged Information:**  
We personally do not collect any information on consumers who browse our Web page.

**Email Addresses:**  
The only email addresses that are collected by JoBlo.com are those volunteered by our visitors for our 1) Message Boards and b) Our Mailing list. These addresses are only used to communicate with the opt-in visitors when needed, and are not sold, distributed or shown to any third party company. Furthermore, visitors may choose to opt-out of receiving any future mailings.

We also run contests from time to time, in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their name and mailing address). This information if used only for the delivery of prizes and to identify cheaters, and nothing else. Once the contest is over, we delete all of that information from our records.

**External Links:  
**This site contains links to other sites. JoBlo.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Public Forums:**  
This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Contacting the Web Site:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact me, Berge Garabedian at [joblo@joblo.com.  
](mailto:joblo@joblo.com)
